

Akash Bavale

Software Engineer

A result-oriented professional with 6+ years of experience in Software Development which includes working on technologies such as Angular, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Html following Agile Methodology. Looking to grow stronger technically and build a stable career in a healthy environment which not only provides me opportunities to work, utilize my competencies to the best, but also helps me explore myself and give my best to the organization.

bavaleakash@gmail.com

Pune, India

bavaleakash.github.io

+91 9028385958

21 September, 1991

S bavaleakash

WORK EXPERIENCE

Harman Connected Services Senior Engineer

08/2019 - Present Client Location: Schlumberger India 1 Year +

Smartek21Software Engineer

05/2018 - 08/2019 1 Year 3 Months

Achievements

- SmartTeam Award for SHMS

NIhilent Technologies System Engineer

05/2015 - 05/2018 3 Years

Achievements

- Team Award for Fundamo

Mphasis Ltd.

Technical Support Associate

07/2013 - 03/2014 9 Months

EDUCATION

B.E (Electronics)

MIT-AOE, Pune

2013 63.33%

HSC

SNBP, Pimpri

2009 62%

SSC

Tata Motors Vidya Niketan, Pune

2007 68%

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Agora: Harman/Schlumberger (2019 - Present)

- Angular, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, NodeJS/NestJS, GraphQL, Azure
- Agora is an initiative of Schlumberger India, which visualizes the data coming from sensors attached to Oil Wells such as ESP, SRP, Vx

SHMS (Sales Hierarchy Management System) : Smartek21 (2018)

- Anguar 4, Bootstrap 4, CSS3, HTML 5
- The project dealt with the management of the hierarchy of the store and the people working in the respective stores. It mostly consisted of the converting an already existing excel project into a web based project using the technologies such as angular, java, sql.

MFSA School Fees: Nihilent Technologies (2017)

- Anguar 4, Bootstrap 4, CSS3, HTML 5, Core JAVA, Spring, Hibernate, RESTful Web Servces
- School Fees is developed, hosted and maintained as open-source tool for schools to digitally manage school operations including students and tuition payments.

Fundamo Mobile Money Implementation(R3): Nihilent Technologies (2015)

- Core JAVA, JavaScript, WebServices
- This is a Mobile Wallet implementation using Fundamo mobile platform as core of it. This project customizes the Fundamo implementation for respective telecom client to enable various mobile transactions from mobile phone by the means of internet and USSD.

COURSES

Diploma in Advanced Computing (CDAC) (08/2014 - 02/2015)

CDAC-Akurdi, Pune